<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/code/pfs.css"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A List of all the Irish army in Ireland under the late King James with other important affairs relating to that Kingdom.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 11KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 2 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2016-02">2016-02 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A48641</idno><idno type="EEBO-CITATION">7940444</idno>
  <idno type="VID">40573</idno>
  <idno type="EEBO-PROQUEST">2264208479</idno>
  
            <idno type="STC">Wing L2380A</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R24008</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">07940444</idno>
            <availability><p>This keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above is co-owned by the
    institutions providing financial support to the Early English Books Online Text Creation
    Partnership. This text is available for reuse, according to the terms of <ref target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"> Creative Commons 0 1.0 Universal
    licence</ref>. The text can be copied, modified, distributed and performed, even for commercial
    purposes, all without asking permission.</p></availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt><relatedItem type="facs" target="https://data.historicaltexts.jisc.ac.uk/view?pubId=eebo-e"/>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A48641)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 40573)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1209:15)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A List of all the Irish army in Ireland under the late King James with other important affairs relating to that Kingdom.</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[2] p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Printed for William Faulkner,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1690]</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Caption title.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,363 texts created during Phase 1 of the project have been released into the public domain as of 1 January 2015. Anyone can now take and use these texts for their own purposes, but we respectfully request that due credit and attribution is given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Full documentation of the original data capture process is available from the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.
   All versions of the texts are now archived and freely available for download. See <ref target="https://textcreationpartnership.org/faq/#faq05">the TCP Download FAQ</ref>
   for detailed information. The TEI P5 versions are also freely available from the <ref target="https://github.com/textcreationpartnership">TCP Github repository</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp" matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)" replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char" matchPattern="(.+)" replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term type="geographic_name">Ireland --  History --  James II, 1685-1688 --  Sources.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2014-05 </date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-08 </date>
            <label>John Pas </label>Sampled and proofread </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-08 </date>
            <label>John Pas</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited </change>
         <change>
            <date>2015-03 </date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion </change>
      <change><date>2021-05 </date><label>lb</label>TEI P5 conversion </change></revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <body>
         <div type="text">
            <pb facs="tcp:40573:1"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:40573:1"/>
            <head>A LIST Of all the Irish Army in Ireland Under the late King <hi>JAMES.</hi> WITH OTHER Important Affairs Relating to that Kingdom.</head>
            <div type="part">
               <opener>
                  <salute>SIR,</salute>
               </opener>
               <p>I Have yours of the 8th Instant, and finding News acceptable, tho I can<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>not promise all mine at first hand, yet such as I meet with from Credi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>
                  <gap reason="illegible: left margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                     <desc>•…</desc>
                  </gap>le Persons, I here send you. The List on the other side I am informed was the state of King <hi>Jame</hi>'s Army in <hi>February</hi> last, as taken out of the Muster-Rolls; I have it from a good hand, and believe the most material parts of it to be true, tho 'tis possible enough there may be some small mistake in Names: This will acquaint you with the state of their Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>my. Ours here is in very good Conditi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on. The <hi>Danes</hi> are all very Expert Sol<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>diers, and as likely to do Service as any Men I ever saw. They are well Cloath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed, and I believe well paid. We hear from some who left <hi>Dublin,</hi> that the late King <hi>James</hi> was building Hutts round the City, and also round the Wall of the Park, for the Horse to lie in—they add, That Quarrels often hap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pen between the <hi>French</hi> and the <hi>Irish;</hi> that it was usual for the <hi>French</hi> to Plunder the Protestants Houses, and take what Provisions they had—They further say, That a Party of the Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rison at <hi>Belturbet</hi> Marched all Night a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bout Twelve Miles space, to that which was the Lady <hi>Hamiltons</hi> House, where<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>in was a Garrison of 300 <hi>Irish;</hi> upon which our men threatned them, that in case they would not Surrender, they must expect no Quarter from them; upon which they Surrendered it; where<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>in there was much Provision, and car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ried away with them 120 Cattle that were Grazing near that place.</p>
               <p>Three hundred and fifty Firelocks of Colonel St. <hi>Johns</hi> Regiment, and a Troop of <hi>Inniskillin Dragoons,</hi> Marched from <hi>Armagh</hi> to <hi>Castle-Blany,</hi> to beat up the Enemies Quarters, and in sight of twice the Number, brought away 200 <hi>l</hi>'s worth of black Cattle. A considerable Party of our Forces have fallen upon the <hi>Irish</hi> at <hi>Charlemount,</hi> got within their utmost Trenches, and given 'em a great defeat. We have here a fine Spring, God be Blessed, and the Feavour is al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>most totally abated. If any have it, it is not so Malignant by much, as hereto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fore. There are now a great many Sail of Ships here waiting for a Wind for <hi>England.</hi> The <hi>Mary</hi>-Gally which Rows, loos'd this day, being fair Wea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther, though the Wind at <hi>N. E.</hi> or there abouts, strong against her. The <hi>Dart<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mouth</hi> and other two are order'd for the <hi>High Lands</hi> of <hi>Scotland.</hi> Pray Sir, now and then favour me with some of your <hi>English</hi> News, for we get little here; my Service to your Lady and Friends. I am</p>
               <closer>
                  <signed>Your Affectionate Friend and Humble Servant.</signed>
               </closer>
            </div>
            <div type="list">
               <pb facs="tcp:40573:2"/>
               <head>A <hi>LIST</hi> of the <hi>Irish</hi> Army in <hi>Ireland,</hi> under the late King <hi>James.</hi>
               </head>
               <p>
                  <table>
                     <head>HORSE.</head>
                     <row>
                        <cell> </cell>
                        <cell role="label">Troops</cell>
                        <cell role="label">Men</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Tyrconnel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>9</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Galway</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>9</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Sarsfield</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>9</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Butler</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>8</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Abercorn</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>8</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Henry Lutterel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>8</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Parker</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>8</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Nicholas Pursel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>10</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell cols="3">
                           <hi>In all</hi>—Eight Regiments, Containing 2450 Men.</cell>
                     </row>
                  </table>
               </p>
               <p>
                  <table>
                     <head>DRAGOONS.</head>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Dungan</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>10</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sr. <hi>William Neagle</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>10</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Daniel O Brian</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>12</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Simon Lutterel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>10</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Clifford</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>10</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sr. <hi>James Cotterel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>12</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Maxwell</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>12</cell>
                        <cell>50</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell cols="3">
                           <hi>In all</hi>—Seven Regiments, Contain<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing 3800 Men besides the Troop of Guards Commanded by the Lord <hi>Dover.</hi>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                  </table>
               </p>
               <p>
                  <table>
                     <head>FOOT.</head>
                     <row>
                        <cell> </cell>
                        <cell role="label">Comp</cell>
                        <cell role="label">Men</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>
                           <hi>Regiment of Guards</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>20</cell>
                        <cell>90</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Mountcastle</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Earl of <hi>Clanearty</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Fitz-James</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Hambleton</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Earl of <hi>Clanrickard</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Earl of <hi>Antrim</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Earl of <hi>Tyrone</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Gormonstown</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Clare</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Galway</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Slane</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <gap reason="blank" extent="1 word">
                              <desc> _____ </desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Duleke</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sir <gap reason="blank" extent="1 word">
                              <desc> _____ </desc>
                           </gap>
                           <hi>Brown</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sr <hi>John Fitz-gerald</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sr. <hi>Maurice Eustace</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>William Nugent</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Henry Dillon</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Grace</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Richard Butler</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Edward Butler</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Thomas Butler</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Bourk</hi> now Lord <hi>Raphni</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Charles Moore</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Cormuch O Neil</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Arthur Mac Mahon</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <gap reason="blank" extent="1 word">
                              <desc> _____ </desc>
                           </gap>
                           <hi>Westmeath</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Charles Cavenagh</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Henry Oxburgh</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Charle<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                                 <desc>•</desc>
                              </gap> Mac-Carty Moor</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Gerrard O Neile</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Browne</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Barrett</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col <hi>Daniel O Duvan</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>6<gap reason="illegible: right margin cropped or obscured" resp="#keyers" extent="1+ letters">
                              <desc>•…</desc>
                           </gap>
                        </cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Oliver O G</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sir <hi>Michael Creagh</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Sir <hi>Daniel Brown</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col <hi>Dudl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                                 <desc>•</desc>
                              </gap>y Bagnel</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Charles O Bryan</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col <hi>Roger Macquillicutt</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>K<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                                 <desc>•</desc>
                              </gap>lmallock</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Lord <hi>Iveagh</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>John Browne</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Edward Newgent</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Mac Maghan</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Edward Reyly</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell>Col. <hi>Fielding</hi>
                        </cell>
                        <cell>13</cell>
                        <cell>62</cell>
                     </row>
                     <row>
                        <cell cols="3">In all 48 Regiments, containing 39400 Men.</cell>
                     </row>
                  </table>
               </p>
               <list>
                  <head>Thirteen Regiments disbanded, <hi>viz.</hi>
                  </head>
                  <item>Major General <hi>Bayloe.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Lord <hi>Castleconnel.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>Roger O Conner.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Sir <hi>Christopher Geogham.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>Mannus O Donnel.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>James Butler.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>Roger O Cahan.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>Christopher Kelly.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>Bryan Mac Dermot.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. <hi>James Talbot.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Sir <hi>Ʋlick Bourk.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Sir <hi>Edward Scott.</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>Col. Miles Kelly.</item>
               </list>
            </div>
         </div>
         <div type="publishers_advertisement">
            <head>ADVERTISEMENTS.</head>
            <p>☞ There is publisht a new Play Entituled, The late Revolution: Or the happy Change. A Tragi-Comedy, as it was acted throughout the English Dominions in the Year 1688. Written by a Person of Quality.</p>
            <p>☞ An Antidote against Lust. By R. C. Minister.</p>
         </div>
      </body>
      <back>
         <div type="colophon">
            <p>
               <hi>LONDON:</hi> Printed for <hi>William Faulkner</hi> in the <hi>Old-Bayly,</hi> 1690.</p>
         </div>
      </back>
   </text>
</TEI>